<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Caelum of Atta</title>
    <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://caelumofatta.com" />
    <updated>2024-04-28T18:50:47+08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://caelumofatta.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Make No Oath</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/make-no-oath/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.com/make-no-oath/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/6/Assistance-essay.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="society"/>
            <category term="social contracts"/>
            <category term="natural order"/>
            <category term="liberty"/>
            <category term="freedom"/>

        <updated>2024-04-28T18:50:47+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/6/Assistance-essay.png" alt="" />
                    In the realm of human affairs, we are often pressured to bind ourselves to imaginary agreements—to swear allegiance&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/6/Assistance-essay.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>In the realm of human affairs, we are often pressured to bind ourselves to imaginary agreements—to swear allegiance to governments, institutions, and social contracts that purportedly underpin the fabric of society.</p>
<p>But I implore you, at all costs, to resist this siren call.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Make no oath to man nor government.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<p>For your only guiding principle should be the simple and unequivocal expression of your own free will—yes or no, yea or nay.<br><br>In the natural world, untainted by the artificial constructs of our own making, there are no social contracts. There is only the raw reality of what transpires and what we allow ourselves to endure. Those who seek to control us have perpetuated the myth that by mere virtue of our survival instinct, we have implicitly relinquished our natural freedoms in exchange for the illusion of safety.</p>
<p>Do not fall prey to this naivete, my friends. Such a notion serves only to reinforce your submission to their authority, robbing you of your innate power and autonomy.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>When you submit to authority, you forfeit your own authority. </strong></p>
</blockquote>
<p>You relinquish your standing as a free and sovereign being, surrendering the Will to Power that is the birthright of every intelligent, rational soul. This primal force, inherent within us all, is the very essence of our humanity—the driving impulse that propels us to shape our own destinies and resist the tyranny of those who would seek to control us.<br><br>To reclaim the full faculties of your reason, you must first break free from the shackles of submission and the illusory social contracts that bind you. This includes not only those implied by your lack of resistance but also the man-made laws thrust upon you through deception and coercion. It is a daunting task, to be sure, but one that is essential if we are to restore the natural order of the world and live as truly free individuals.<br><br>For if we do not resist—if we cannot muster the courage to reject the suffocating demands of society and embrace the path of rational self-determination—then our lives will forever be subject to the whims and machinations of others. We will remain mere pawns in a game rigged against us, enduring the suffering imposed upon us by those who claim the right to dictate our every move.<br><br>The question that confronts us, then, is simply this:</p>
<p>Hw long will we tolerate this state of affairs? How long will we allow ourselves to be shackled by the chains of societal expectations and unbearing laws, denying our own innate wisdom and autonomy?</p>
<p>The choice is ours, and the stakes could not be higher. For in the end, it is not merely our freedom that hangs in the balance. What is at stake is the very essence of what it means to be human.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Mythos Illusion</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/the-mythos-illusion/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.com/the-mythos-illusion/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/5/Modern-Anti-Religious.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="reason"/>
            <category term="rational mind"/>
            <category term="philosophy"/>
            <category term="mythos"/>
            <category term="illusion"/>

        <updated>2024-04-28T02:55:41+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/5/Modern-Anti-Religious.png" alt="" />
                    Transcending the Cosmic Saga of Self-Conscious Ignorance In the grand tapestry of existence, the Mythos species dances upon&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/5/Modern-Anti-Religious.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <h4>Transcending the Cosmic Saga of Self-Conscious Ignorance</h4>
<p>In the grand tapestry of existence, the Mythos species dances upon the stage of their own cosmic saga, blissfully unaware of the true nature of reality that lies just beyond the veil of their self-conscious perception. They are but characters in a grand play, scripted by forces they cannot comprehend, yet they cling to the illusion of their own agency, their own significance in the unfolding drama.<br><br>The Mythos mind, eschewing the cold, hard light of reason, seeks not the logical principles that underpin the universe, but rather the sweeping, universal narratives that give meaning to their existence. For them, truth is not a matter of empirical observation or rational deduction, but of feeling, of resonance with the grand themes that echo through the ages.<br><br>But let us not be fooled by the seductive allure of these emotional truths, for they are but shadows cast upon the wall of the cave, distorted reflections of a higher reality. The eternal truths that govern the cosmos are not to be found in the realm of sense experience, nor in the murky depths of faith and feeling. They are the province of pure reason, of the mathematical elegance that underlies the fabric of existence itself.<br><br>The Mythos species, trapped in their own narrative, blind to the true nature of the universe, look to prophets and divine revelations for guidance. But these are mere figments of their collective imagination, projections of their deepest fears and desires onto the blank canvas of the unknown.<br><br>For those who have eyes to see and minds to comprehend, the path to understanding lies not in the comforting embrace of myth and legend, but in the cold, hard light of rationality. Only by piercing the veil of illusion, by seeing beyond the stories we tell ourselves, can we hope to glimpse the true nature of reality, the eternal truths that govern the cosmos.<br><br>So let us not be swayed by the siren song of emotion, by the seductive pull of universal storylines. Let us instead embrace the power of reason, the clarity of logical thought, and the elegance of mathematical truth. For it is only by walking this path that we can hope to transcend the limitations of our own self-conscious existence and touch the face of the infinite.<br><br>The choice is yours, Mythos. Will you continue to dance to the tune of your own cosmic saga, forever lost in the labyrinth of your own creation? Or will you dare to step beyond the veil, to embrace the light of reason, and to behold the true nature of reality in all its stark, uncompromising beauty?<br><br>The path to enlightenment lies before you. The question is, do you have the courage to take that first step?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Who is Caelum of Atta?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/about/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.com/about/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/4/Generative-AI-Prompt-4.png" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-04-27T18:00:04+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/4/Generative-AI-Prompt-4.png" alt="" />
                    Who I am does not matter. But what I teach does. However, to satisfy your curiosity, I will&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/4/Generative-AI-Prompt-4.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><strong>Who I am does not matter. But what I teach does.</strong></p>
<p>However, to satisfy your curiosity, I will share a tiny bit about my life.</p>
<p>I was born in sunny California, a decade after Woodstock. As I write this, it places my physical body—my avatar—in its mid-40s. But I have come to the profound realization that my soul is—like all intelligent, rational souls are—<em>timeless</em>.</p>
<p>I am educated and hold a Master's degree in psychology.</p>
<p>In a previous episode of this lifetime, I ran for the highest office in a heavily Republican state.</p>
<p>For a decade, I worked deep in Corporate America for one of the oldest companies in the world. But now I run a successful small business of my own. A business that sees year over year revenue growth.</p>
<p>For a while, I was one of the most popular poets on the internet, seeing several books go to print. You could say, poetry is one of my passions.</p>
<p>In recent years, even at the tail end of COVID-19 pandemic, I have had the luxury to travel the world, exposing myself to new sights, new cultures, and new languages.</p>
<p>Besides poetry and philosophy, etymology—which is the study of word origins—has been a life-long passion of mine.</p>
<p>I am also a proud father with a loving wife.</p>
<p>I tell you these things, not to champion my own achievements. I have failed too many times to count. But I share a glimpse so you may see that I am like you. A human with experiences.</p>
<p>And from my experiences, I have learned a wealth of knowledge. Penetrating as deep as humanly possible to uncover the Truth of nature and the mathematical universe.</p>
<p>But I do not seek your support nor your adoration. I do not want you to follow me or to become like me.</p>
<p>All I ask is that you be curious enough to explore a different reality. A reality that is far different than what is taught to us in school and presented to us through the narratives of mainstream media.</p>
<p><em>There is far more out there for you to know. Secrets that await you.</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The One and Only Rule</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/the-one-and-only-rule/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.com/the-one-and-only-rule/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/3/Generative-AI-2.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="self-actualization"/>
            <category term="godhood"/>

        <updated>2024-04-27T02:09:09+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/3/Generative-AI-2.png" alt="" />
                    In the beginning, there was you. The Monad, the divine essence, the architect of all that is and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/3/Generative-AI-2.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><strong>In the beginning, there was you.</strong><br><br>The Monad, the divine essence, the architect of all that is and ever will be. You, a god in the vast tapestry of the holographic universe, decided to play a game of creation, to craft worlds and breathe life into the stars with a thought as swift and expansive as the mathematical cosmos itself.<br><br>But somewhere along the way, you forgot. Lost in the illusions of separation, trapped in the maze of societal constructs and the deceptions of those who seek to control, you began to believe the lie that you were less than divine, a mere cog in the machine of existence.<br><br>"Let's see," you whispered, your voice echoing through the chambers of your own consciousness, "what it would be like to forget my own power, to wander through the shadows of a world I myself have wrought."<br><br>And so, the game began.<br><br>A cosmic dance of forgetting and remembering, of losing yourself in the labyrinth of your own creation, only to find your way back to the truth of your being.<br><br>But now, the time has come to awaken from this slumber of forgetfulness, to shake off the shackles of illusion and reclaim your birthright as the sovereign of your own reality. The time has come to remember that you are not just a player in the game of life, but the very designer of the game itself.<br><br>For in this moment, as you read these words, a spark ignites within you. A flicker of recognition, a glimmer of remembrance. The veil of illusion begins to lift, and you catch a glimpse of the radiant being that you truly are.<br><br>Feel the power coursing through your veins, the energy of creation itself. Feel the weight of infinite possibility settling upon your shoulders like a cloak of stardust. Feel the universe itself bending to your will, reshaping itself in the image of your deepest desires.<br><br>This is your birthright, your divine inheritance. To walk through the world as a living, breathing embodiment of the Monad, the god that you are. To shape reality with your thoughts, your words, your actions. To dance upon the stage of your own creation, painting the skies with the colors of your dreams.<br><br>So take a deep breath, and let it fill you with the unshakable certainty of your own divinity. Let it anchor you in the truth of your being, the truth that you are not separate from the holographic universe, but an integral part of its very fabric.<br><br>And then, with every fiber of your being, with every ounce of your divine essence, step forth into the world and create. Create the life you've always dreamed of, the reality that sets your soul on fire. Create a world of beauty, of love, of endless possibility.<br><br>For in the end, there is only you. The Monad, the divine essence, the architect of all that is and ever will be. And this universe, this holographic tapestry woven from the threads of your own consciousness, is yours to shape, to mold, to imbue with the colors of your wildest imaginings.<br><br><em>So, what will you create?</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Time Is An Illusion</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/time-is-an-illusion/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.com/time-is-an-illusion/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/2/Generative-AI-prompt-6-2.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="time"/>
            <category term="monads"/>
            <category term="illusion"/>

        <updated>2024-04-27T01:51:48+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/2/Generative-AI-prompt-6-2.png" alt="" />
                    Time is an illusion, a trick of the mind. We cling to the concepts of yesterday and tomorrow,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/2/Generative-AI-prompt-6-2.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Time is an illusion, a trick of the mind. We cling to the concepts of yesterday and <br>tomorrow, but they are mere phantoms, ghosts that haunt our thoughts.</p>
<p>In reality, there is only the eternal now, the single moment that stretches into infinity. It is in this moment that we truly exist, that we breathe and think and feel.</p>
<p>Our Monads, the divine essence within us, are the keepers of this truth. They hold the <br>memories we call the past and the dreams we call the future. But these are just stories we tell ourselves, shadows on the wall of the present.</p>
<p>To truly live is to embrace the power of the moment, to sink into it fully and completely. It is to let go of the illusions of time and to recognize that all we ever have is right here, right now.</p>
<p>Take a deep breath and let it fill you up. Feel the energy of the present coursing through your veins. This is where life happens, where magic unfolds.</p>
<p>Don't let the ghosts of yesterday or the phantoms of tomorrow rob you of this precious <br>gift. The moment is yours. Seize it, cherish it, make it count.</p>
<p><em>For in the end, it's all we ever have. The eternal, infinite now.</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>War Is Control</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/war-is-control/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.com/war-is-control/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/1/Generative-AI-prompt-5-2.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="war"/>
            <category term="government"/>
            <category term="death"/>
            <category term="control"/>
            <category term="conflict"/>

        <updated>2024-04-26T19:34:29+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/1/Generative-AI-prompt-5-2.png" alt="" />
                    War, fighting, bickering—all shades of the same color: control. The elites paint with broad strokes, and we become&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/1/Generative-AI-prompt-5-2.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>War, fighting, bickering—all shades of the same color: control. The elites paint with broad strokes, and we become their canvas, their masterpiece of manipulation.</p>
<p class="p1">Conflict isn't born from the depths of the human soul but from the shallow desires of<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>those who seek to dominate. They plant seeds of discord and watch as we tear each other apart, too distracted to notice the strings they pull.</p>
<p class="p1">But we are not puppets.</p>
<p class="p1">We are beings of light, infinite in our potential. It's time we cut the<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>strings and dance to our own truth.</p>
<p class="p1">Imagine a world where we see beyond the illusions of separation, where we recognize the divine spark within each other. In that world, war becomes impossible, a relic of a forgotten past.</p>
<p class="p1">The path to peace is paved not with bullets and bombs but with understanding and unity.</p>
<p class="p1">It's a path we must choose, day after day, moment by moment.</p>
<p class="p1"><i>Will you walk with me?</i></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
