<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Caelum of Atta</title>
    <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://caelumofatta.com" />
    <updated>2024-04-28T23:51:54+08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://caelumofatta.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Make No Oath</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/make-no-oath/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.com/make-no-oath/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/6/Make-No-Oath-Caelum-of-Atta.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="society"/>
            <category term="social contracts"/>
            <category term="natural order"/>
            <category term="liberty"/>
            <category term="freedom"/>

        <updated>2024-04-28T18:50:47+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/6/Make-No-Oath-Caelum-of-Atta.png" alt="" />
                    In the realm of human affairs, we are often pressured to bind ourselves to imaginary agreements—to swear allegiance&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/6/Make-No-Oath-Caelum-of-Atta.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>In the realm of human affairs, we are often pressured to bind ourselves to imaginary agreements—to swear allegiance to governments, institutions, and social contracts that purportedly underpin the fabric of society.</p>
<p>But I implore you, at all costs, to resist this siren call.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>Make no oath to man nor government.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<p>For your only guiding principle should be the simple and unequivocal expression of your own free will—yes or no, yea or nay.<br><br>In the natural world, untainted by the artificial constructs of our own making, there are no social contracts. There is only the raw reality of what transpires and what we allow ourselves to endure. Those who seek to control us have perpetuated the myth that by mere virtue of our survival instinct, we have implicitly relinquished our natural freedoms in exchange for the illusion of safety.</p>
<p>Do not fall prey to this naivete, my friends. Such a notion serves only to reinforce your submission to their authority, robbing you of your innate power and autonomy.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>When you submit to authority, you forfeit your own authority. </strong></p>
</blockquote>
<p>You relinquish your standing as a free and sovereign being, surrendering the Will to Power that is the birthright of every intelligent, rational soul. This primal force, inherent within us all, is the very essence of our humanity—the driving impulse that propels us to shape our own destinies and resist the tyranny of those who would seek to control us.<br><br>To reclaim the full faculties of your reason, you must first break free from the shackles of submission and the illusory social contracts that bind you. This includes not only those implied by your lack of resistance but also the man-made laws thrust upon you through deception and coercion. It is a daunting task, to be sure, but one that is essential if we are to restore the natural order of the world and live as truly free individuals.<br><br>For if we do not resist—if we cannot muster the courage to reject the suffocating demands of society and embrace the path of rational self-determination—then our lives will forever be subject to the whims and machinations of others. We will remain mere pawns in a game rigged against us, enduring the suffering imposed upon us by those who claim the right to dictate our every move.<br><br>The question that confronts us, then, is simply this:</p>
<p>Hw long will we tolerate this state of affairs? How long will we allow ourselves to be shackled by the chains of societal expectations and overbearing laws, denying our own innate wisdom and autonomy?</p>
<p>The choice is ours, and the stakes could not be higher. For in the end, it is not merely our freedom that hangs in the balance. What is at stake is the very essence of what it means to be human.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Who is Caelum of Atta?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.com/about/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.com/about/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/4/Who-Is-Caelum-of-Atta.png" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-04-27T18:00:04+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/4/Who-Is-Caelum-of-Atta.png" alt="" />
                    Who I am does not matter. But what I teach does. However, to satisfy your curiosity, I will&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.com/media/posts/4/Who-Is-Caelum-of-Atta.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><strong>Who I am does not matter.</strong></p>
<p><strong>But what I teach does.</strong></p>
<p>However, to satisfy your curiosity, I will share a tiny bit about my life.</p>
<p>I was born in sunny California, a decade after Woodstock. As I write this, it places my physical body—my avatar—in its mid-40s. But I have come to the profound realization that my soul is—like all intelligent, rational souls are—<em>timeless</em>.</p>
<p>I am educated and hold a Master's degree in psychology.</p>
<p>In a previous episode of this lifetime, I ran for the highest office in a heavily Republican state.</p>
<p>For a decade, I worked deep in Corporate America for one of the oldest companies in the world. But now I run a successful small business of my own. A business that sees year over year revenue growth.</p>
<p>For a while, I was one of the most popular poets on the internet, seeing several books go to print. You could say, poetry is one of my passions.</p>
<p>In recent years, even at the tail end of COVID-19 pandemic, I have had the luxury to travel the world, exposing myself to new sights, new cultures, and new languages.</p>
<p>Besides poetry and philosophy, etymology—which is the study of word origins—has been a life-long passion of mine.</p>
<p>I am also a proud father with a loving wife.</p>
<p>I tell you these things, not to champion my own achievements. I have failed too many times to count. But I share a glimpse so you may see that I am like you. A human with experiences.</p>
<p>And from my experiences, I have learned a wealth of knowledge. Penetrating as deep as humanly possible to uncover the Truth of nature and the mathematical universe.</p>
<p>But I do not seek your support nor your adoration. I do not want you to follow me or to become like me.</p>
<p>All I ask is that you be curious enough to explore a different reality. A reality that is far different than what is taught to us in school and presented to us through the narratives of mainstream media.</p>
<p><em>There is far more out there for you to know. Secrets that await you.</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
