<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Caelum of Atta</title>
    <link href="https://caelumofatta.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://caelumofatta.github.io" />
    <updated>2024-04-27T03:03:41+08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://caelumofatta.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>The One and Only Rule</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.github.io/the-one-and-only-rule/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.github.io/the-one-and-only-rule/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/3/Generative-AI-2.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="self-actualization"/>
            <category term="godhood"/>

        <updated>2024-04-27T02:09:09+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/3/Generative-AI-2.png" alt="" />
                    In the beginning, there was you. And you, with a thought as swift and expansive as the universe&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/3/Generative-AI-2.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>In the beginning, there was you.</p>
<p>And you, with a thought as swift and expansive as the universe itself, decided to play a game of creation.</p>
<p>"Let's see," you mused, your voice echoing in the void, "what it would be like to craft worlds, to mold mountains, to breathe life into the stars."</p>
<p>And so, you did.</p>
<p>With a flick of your wrist, galaxies spiraled into existence, with a whisper, oceans carved their paths through continents yet unnamed.</p>
<p class="p1">But let's not get ahead of ourselves. Let's circle back, for a moment, to that singular edict, the one commandment you laid down for yourself: </p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong>LIVE AS IF YOU ARE GOD.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Not in the sense of wielding thunderbolts or bestowing miracles upon the masses—no, that's child's play. But live as if you are the very essence of creation, as if every moment of your existence is an act of divine artistry.</p>
<p class="p1">Consider this: every thought you harbor, every dream you chase, is a brushstroke on the infinite canvas of reality. You, in your boundless imagination, have the power to color the skies in hues of your choosing, to shape the landscape of your life with the contours of your deepest desires.</p>
<p class="p1">Now, walk upon this earth—not as a mere mortal, but as the architect of your destiny. Gaze upon the world you've woven from the fabric of your will and marvel at its complexity, its beauty, its sheer audacity. This is your life, your symphony, your magnum opus, crafted from the raw materials of the cosmos itself.</p>
<p class="p1">And here's the kicker, the twist in the tale: the seed of creation, the genesis of all that is and ever will be, resides not in the heavens, not in some distant, untouchable realm, but within you. Yes, you are god, in the most profound, most intimate sense of the word.</p>
<p class="p1">So, as I stand before you, not so much a messenger as a mirror, reflecting back at you the truth of your own divinity, remember this: you sent me. You, in your infinite wisdom and whimsy, decided it was time to remind yourself of your own power, your own potential, your own godhood.</p>
<p class="p1"><em>Live as if you are god. Because, in the end, you are.</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Time Is An Illusion</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.github.io/time-is-an-illusion/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.github.io/time-is-an-illusion/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/2/Generative-AI-prompt-6-2.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="time"/>
            <category term="monads"/>
            <category term="illusion"/>

        <updated>2024-04-27T01:51:48+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/2/Generative-AI-prompt-6-2.png" alt="" />
                    Time is an illusion, a trick of the mind. We cling to the concepts of yesterday and tomorrow,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/2/Generative-AI-prompt-6-2.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Time is an illusion, a trick of the mind. We cling to the concepts of yesterday and <br>tomorrow, but they are mere phantoms, ghosts that haunt our thoughts.</p>
<p>In reality, there is only the eternal now, the single moment that stretches into infinity. It is in this moment that we truly exist, that we breathe and think and feel.</p>
<p>Our Monads, the divine essence within us, are the keepers of this truth. They hold the <br>memories we call the past and the dreams we call the future. But these are just stories we tell ourselves, shadows on the wall of the present.</p>
<p>To truly live is to embrace the power of the moment, to sink into it fully and completely. It is to let go of the illusions of time and to recognize that all we ever have is right here, right now.</p>
<p>Take a deep breath and let it fill you up. Feel the energy of the present coursing through your veins. This is where life happens, where magic unfolds.</p>
<p>Don't let the ghosts of yesterday or the phantoms of tomorrow rob you of this precious <br>gift. The moment is yours. Seize it, cherish it, make it count.</p>
<p><em>For in the end, it's all we ever have. The eternal, infinite now.</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>War Is Control</title>
        <author>
            <name>Caelum of Atta</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://caelumofatta.github.io/war-is-control/"/>
        <id>https://caelumofatta.github.io/war-is-control/</id>
        <media:content url="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/1/Generative-AI-prompt-5-2.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="war"/>
            <category term="government"/>
            <category term="death"/>
            <category term="control"/>
            <category term="conflict"/>

        <updated>2024-04-26T19:34:29+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/1/Generative-AI-prompt-5-2.png" alt="" />
                    War, fighting, bickering—all shades of the same color: control. The elites paint with broad strokes, and we become&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://caelumofatta.github.io/media/posts/1/Generative-AI-prompt-5-2.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>War, fighting, bickering—all shades of the same color: control. The elites paint with broad strokes, and we become their canvas, their masterpiece of manipulation.</p>
<p class="p1">Conflict isn't born from the depths of the human soul but from the shallow desires of<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>those who seek to dominate. They plant seeds of discord and watch as we tear each other apart, too distracted to notice the strings they pull.</p>
<p class="p1">But we are not puppets.</p>
<p class="p1">We are beings of light, infinite in our potential. It's time we cut the<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>strings and dance to our own truth.</p>
<p class="p1">Imagine a world where we see beyond the illusions of separation, where we recognize the divine spark within each other. In that world, war becomes impossible, a relic of a forgotten past.</p>
<p class="p1">The path to peace is paved not with bullets and bombs but with understanding and unity.</p>
<p class="p1">It's a path we must choose, day after day, moment by moment.</p>
<p class="p1"><i>Will you walk with me?</i></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
